http://www.sunbeltmetal.com/privacypolicy.html

Warning:
preg_replace_callback(): Requires argument 2, 'utf8_encode(chr(\1))', to be a valid callback in /home1/thejoker/sunbeltmetal.com/libraries/joomla/filter/filterinput.php on line 512
Deprecated:
preg_replace(): The /e modifier is deprecated, use preg_replace_callback instead in /home1/thejoker/sunbeltmetal.com/libraries/joomla/filter/filterinput.php on line 514
HomeSlittingBlankingCold ReductionEdgingToll Processing/StorageContact UsPrivacyDocs
&quotSmall enough to provide the personal attention you deserve….Large enough to meet your expectation for quality and timely service at a competitive price."
Home
Privacy
Warning:
preg_replace_callback(): Requires argument 2, 'utf8_encode(chr(\1))', to be a valid callback in /home1/thejoker/sunbeltmetal.com/libraries/joomla/filter/filterinput.php on line 512
Deprecated:
preg_replace(): The /e modifier is deprecated, use preg_replace_callback instead in /home1/thejoker/sunbeltmetal.com/libraries/joomla/filter/filterinput.php on line 514
Privacy Policy For Sunbelt Metal Processing, Inc.:
When a visitor visits a website certain pieces of information are collected by the nature of the website technology. Sunbelt Metal Processing, Inc. respects the privacy of the information collected. Sunbelt Metal Processing, Inc. does not sell, share or rent any portion of this information to any third party and does not intend on doing so in the future.
Information Collected
By sending an e-mail through the address
or by sending an e-mail through the “Contact Us” page to submit or request information about Sunbelt Metal Processing, Inc., your e-mail may be saved along with any other information you may provide. That information can be used to contact you in future communications by e-mail, mail and/or phone to convey information about the products and services offered by Sunbelt Metal Processing, Inc. that may be of interest and benefit to you. The information provided by you by your e-mail transactions will not be sold to any third party.
Information Collected By Others
This notice refers only to the privacy of the Sunbelt Metal Processing, Inc. website and not to any other sites or links that users may use to access our site. Sunbelt Metal Processing, Inc. is not and will not be responsible for the information collection policies of other sites or for the practices used by websites linked to or from our website or for the content and information contained in the other sites. Links to other websites are solely provider to our visitors as pointers to topics and information that may be of interest and/or beneficial. Please review the privacy policies of these other websites.
Correcting, Updating And Deleting Personal Information
Please send an e-mail through our “Contact Us” page with “Remove personal information” in the subject line to have your personal information removed by Sunbelt Metal Processing, Inc. Please send an e-mail with the appropriate changes through our “Contact Us” page to have your personal information changed, updated or corrected by Sunbelt Metal Processing, Inc.
Legally Compelled Disclosure Of Information
Sunbelt Metal Processing, Inc. may be legally compelled to disclose information if in good faith we believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.
Correcting, Updating And Deleting Personal Information
Sunbelt Metal Processing, Inc. does review it’s privacy policy and practices occasionally to check for technology and/or legal changes that may need to be changed. Please bookmark and periodically review this page for any changes to our privacy policies.
Effective April 6, 2012, this statement is made in the name of Sunbelt Metal Processing, Inc. and does not create any agreement between Sunbelt Metal Processing, Inc. and users and does not create any legal rights for any party.
For Inquiries contact:
Sunbelt Metal Processing, Inc. 361 Industrial Park Drive Lawrenceville, GA 30046 Phone:
770-682-3322 Fax:
770-682-5116
Copyright © 2020 Sunbelt Metal. All Rights Reserved.
Joomla! is Free Software released under the GNU/GPL License.
Powered by Joomla!.
valid XHTML and CSS.
